let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the ideal gas law?",
    answer: "PV = nRT",
    options: [
     "P/T = constant",
     "V/T = constant",
     "V/n = constant",
     "PV = nRT"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What does the ideal gas law relate?",
    answer: "Pressure, volume, temperature, and number of moles",
    options: [
     "Pressure and volume",
     "Temperature and number of moles",
     "Pressure and temperature",
     "Volume and number of moles"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the ideal gas constant denoted as?",
    answer: "R",
    options: [
     "P",
     "V",
     "n",
     "R"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What are the units commonly used for the ideal gas constant?",
    answer: "0.08206 L atm mol–1 K–1 and 8.314 kPa L mol–1 K–1",
    options: [
     "0.08206 L atm mol K",
     "8.314 L kPa mol–1 K–1",
     "0.08206 kPa L mol–1 K–1",
     "8.314 L atm mol–1 K–1"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does it mean for a gas to exhibit ideal behavior?",
    answer: "Its properties of P, V, and T are accurately described by the ideal gas law or other gas laws.",
    options: [
     "Its properties of P, V, and T deviate from the ideal gas law.",
     "Its properties of P, V, and T remain constant regardless of conditions.",
     "It follows a random pattern of behavior.",
     "It cannot be described by any gas laws."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Under what conditions does the ideal gas law hold true?",
    answer: "Relatively low pressure and high temperature",
    options: [
     "Relatively high pressure and low temperature",
     "Relatively high pressure and high temperature",
     "Relatively low pressure and low temperature",
     "All pressure and temperature conditions"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the modified gas law used for?",
    answer: "To account for the non-ideal behavior observed for many gases at relatively high pressures and low temperatures.",
    options: [
     "To calculate the properties of an ideal gas.",
     "To simplify gas law calculations.",
     "To describe the behavior of gases under any conditions.",
     "To determine the volume of a gas sample."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which equation represents the ideal gas law?",
    answer: "PV = nRT",
    options: [
     "P/T = constant",
     "V/T = constant",
     "V/n = constant",
     "PV = nRT"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What units must be used for pressure, volume, and temperature in the ideal gas law equation if R = 0.08206 L atm mol–1 K–1?",
    answer: "atm, L, and K",
    options: [
     "kPa, L, and °C",
     "psi, m^3, and °F",
     "torr, cm^3, and °C",
     "pascal, m^3, and K"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the volume of 655 g of CH4 at 25 °C and 745 torr?",
    answer: "1020 L (269 gal)",
    options: [
     "510 L (134.5 gal)",
     "2040 L (538.2 gal)",
     "765 L (202 gal)",
     "1020 L (269 gal)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which term represents the number of moles of a gas in the ideal gas law equation?",
    answer: "n",
    options: [
     "P",
     "V",
     "T",
     "R"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What does the gas constant 'R' represent in the ideal gas law equation?",
    answer: "Ideal gas constant or universal gas constant",
    options: [
     "Pressure",
     "Volume",
     "Number of moles",
     "Ideal gas constant or universal gas constant"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What does it mean for a gas to exhibit ideal behavior?",
    answer: "Its properties of P, V, and T are accurately described by the ideal gas law or other gas laws.",
    options: [
     "Its properties of P, V, and T deviate from the ideal gas law.",
     "Its properties of P, V, and T remain constant regardless of conditions.",
     "It follows a random pattern of behavior.",
     "It cannot be described by any gas laws."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Under what conditions does the ideal gas law hold true?",
    answer: "Relatively low pressure and high temperature",
    options: [
     "Relatively high pressure and low temperature",
     "Relatively high pressure and high temperature",
     "Relatively low pressure and low temperature",
     "All pressure and temperature conditions"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the purpose of the modified gas law?",
    answer: "To account for the non-ideal behavior observed for many gases at relatively high pressures and low temperatures.",
    options: [
     "To calculate the properties of an ideal gas.",
     "To simplify gas law calculations.",
     "To describe the behavior of gases under any conditions.",
     "To determine the volume of a gas sample."
    ]
  },
]
 